we go to our next game turns of ins
searchman turns of
inment when you search for something
online you never know what you're going
to find sometimes you get a cool fact
like how Pluto is the size of Australia
sometimes you get a video of a Corgi
lipsyncing the Save By the Bell theme
and then you're in a bad mood for the
rest of your life comedians get your
buzzer fingers ready I'm going to show
you a picture of something we found on
the Skynet and I want you to tell me the
search term we use to find it uh but
only the first person gets to buzz into
answer and the other two and go suck it
I want to put 60 seconds on the clock
and begin this first
one yes Whitney Andy dicks hard
drive points this
one Nick Whitney's before she
shaved uh Point Nick next
one oh sh uh Whitney Farmers Only
yes next
one Brendan what's uh Scott wiland been
up
[Laughter]
to next how about this llama Brendon uh
Tom Petty
[Laughter]
tickets point for Brandon
yeah Nick fetish starter kit
yep that's it that is the end of terms
of
insurgent